<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>project-management on UNICEF O.S. Inventory</title>
    <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/categories/project-management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in project-management on UNICEF O.S. Inventory</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Creative Commons BY-SA 4.0. Site theme maintained by UNICEF. Original theme, Dot, created by ThemeFisher.</copyright><atom:link href="https://unicef.github.io/inventory/categories/project-management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Issue templates</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/project-management/issue-templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/project-management/issue-templates/</guid>
      <description>This guide is an introduction to issue templates in an Open Source project. While this guide is customized to GitHub, the advice provided here is general and can be applied to other collaboration platforms that offer templating. By the end of this guide, you will have a basic understanding of why issue templates are important and how to set up effective templates for your project. This guide is complementary to an agile or scrum workflow, if your team already uses one of these methods of project management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outreach reading list</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/project-management/reading-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/project-management/reading-list/</guid>
      <description>This reading list focuses on ways to promote and share your Open Source project with the world. Generally these resources are more helpful once you have built up the foundation for your Open Source project. You should have a game plan for community management in place before spending time on outreach.
   What success really looks like in Open Source - Nadia Eghbal @nayafia
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project boards</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/project-management/project-boards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/project-management/project-boards/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents 1. About project boards 1.1. Why?   2. Case study: TeleIRC 3. Examples 4. Additional resources   This guide is an introduction to project boards for your open source project. By the end of this guide, you will have a basic understanding of how to run project planning in an open, transparent way to your community. What this guide is NOT is a guide to agile/scrum development.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
