<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blockchain on UNICEF O.S. Inventory</title>
    <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/cohorts/blockchain/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blockchain on UNICEF O.S. Inventory</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 (CC BY-SA-4.0). Site theme maintained by the [UNICEF Office of Innovation](https://www.unicef.org/innovation/).</copyright><atom:link href="https://unicef.github.io/inventory/cohorts/blockchain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BX Smart Labs</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/cohorts/blockchain/bx-smart-labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/cohorts/blockchain/bx-smart-labs/</guid>
      <description>Decentralised application for saving circles. The payments will be done on the blockchain allowing the saving circles to be built regardless of the location of the users. The smart contract will automatize the payments and withdrawals on each period ensuring the users receive their funds.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kotani Pay</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/cohorts/blockchain/kotani-pay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/cohorts/blockchain/kotani-pay/</guid>
      <description>Kotani Pay is a technology stack that enables blockchain protocols, dapps, and blockchain fintech companies to integrate seamlessly to local payment channels providing them with a reliable on ramp and off ramp service to reach a wider customer base in Africa. Kotani Pay serves as a friction-less bridge between cryptocurrency and fiat currencies and enables users to access the blockchain via USSD. The platform has 300 users to date and is live in Kenya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leaf Global Fintech</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/cohorts/blockchain/leaf-global-fintech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/cohorts/blockchain/leaf-global-fintech/</guid>
      <description>A virtual bank for vulnerable populations, allowing for the storage and transport of assets across borders from a mobile device (without a smartphone). Protects customers’ savings through blockchain technology without exposure to volatile cryptocurrencies. Identity is linked through biometric authentication so that a refugee could lose their documentation and still access their finances.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rumsan</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/cohorts/blockchain/rumsan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/cohorts/blockchain/rumsan/</guid>
      <description>Rumsan is a blockchain innovation company focused on social impact. Rahat, developed by Rumsan, is an open source blockchain-based CVA management system. Rahat manages and monitors the flow of transactions in aid distribution projects. With its real-time visibility to the flow of funds, Rahat builds transparency, accountability and financial inclusivity to maximize support for marginalized communities.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Treejer</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/cohorts/blockchain/treejer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/cohorts/blockchain/treejer/</guid>
      <description>Treejer (trēʒər) is an open protocol connecting funders to rural planters worldwide. The project is experimenting with cutting-edge concepts such as decentralized finance (DeFi), non-fungible tokens (NFTs) and smart contracts to unlock new opportunities for climate finance, rural development and carbon credits. The team has on-boarded planters from over 10 countries located in the Latin America, Africa and Middle East. Users are enabled to make ecological and social impact even in unbanked communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xcapit</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/cohorts/blockchain/xcapit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/cohorts/blockchain/xcapit/</guid>
      <description>A platform using blockchain for wealth management, including financial planning and financial education in a gamified way. The Xcapit team has built an open source and self-custodial wallet and onboarded over 14,000 users from LatAm, especially from Mexico and Argentina within the first 2 months after launching.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
