<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Missions on UNICEF O.S. Inventory</title>
    <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/missions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Missions on UNICEF O.S. Inventory</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Creative Commons BY-SA 4.0. Site theme maintained by UNICEF. Original theme, Dot, created by ThemeFisher.</copyright><atom:link href="https://unicef.github.io/inventory/missions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Charters</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/missions/charters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/missions/charters/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents 1. Launch checklist 1.1. Who? 1.2. What?   2. Preparing for take-off 2.1. Process 2.2. Platform   3. Take-off! Time to launch 3.1. Vision and mission 3.2. Community statement 3.3. Licensing approach 3.4. Code of Conduct 3.5. Trademark identification   4. Destination: Sustainable governance 4.1. Note on revisions   5. References 6. Thanks   This Mission is a guide to project charters. A project charter is important in an Open Source context because it acts as an anchor across the project’s lifetime and provides a framework for making decisions and prioritizing future development work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Codes of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/missions/codes-of-conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/missions/codes-of-conduct/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents 1. Quality of writing 2. Clarity of expectations 3. Defined structure for handling enforcement 4. Two to four people responsible for handling sensitive reports 5. Use an existing Code of Conduct instead of writing one yourself 6. References      This Mission is a short exercise on understanding how Codes of Conduct fit into your Open Source community. In designing a Code of Conduct for a project community, we will explore these Requirements for this Mission:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good first issues</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/missions/good-first-issue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/missions/good-first-issue/</guid>
      <description>Flory, Justin W.
    This Mission is a guide to making &amp;#34;good first issues&amp;#34; (shortened to G.F.I.&amp;#39;s) for your Open Source community. To create good GFIs, we will explore these Objectives for this Mission:
  GFIs exist
  Assignee ratio
  Simple language
  Actionable
  Purpose
  Deadlines
  Low committment
  References
   1. GFIs exist The first requirement to having good GFIs is to… create GFIs!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
