<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hall of fame on UNICEF O.S. Inventory</title>
    <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/tags/hall-of-fame/</link>
    <description>Recent content in hall of fame on UNICEF O.S. Inventory</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Creative Commons BY-SA 4.0</copyright><atom:link href="https://unicef.github.io/inventory/tags/hall-of-fame/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Case studies</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/hardware/case-studies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/hardware/case-studies/</guid>
      <description>Below are more detailed case studios of different Open Hardware organizations, projects, and products. Unlike the Projects page, these examples are more detailed and provide more context.
 Opentrons Scientific-focused hardware.
  Several highly successful and well-regarded biology/chemistry lab automation robots. By going 100% open source, they substantially reduced costs. Their products’ prices sometimes undercuts competition by 10x. They also acquired venture capital (V.C.) funding.
 Having worked in biology labs myself, I can attest to how revolutionary their open source business model is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Documentation Hall of Fame</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/documentation/hall-of-fame/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/documentation/hall-of-fame/</guid>
      <description>This page is a collection of good examples of Open Source documentation projects. The projects and examples listed here are not endorsements. It is a collection of good examples to inspire your own Open Source documentation!
 Aggregations The projects listed below aggregate several existing documentation projects:
   Awesome Documentation: Community-curated resource with examples of great documentation in Open Source projects.
  Awesome Docs with Static Site Generators: This repo is suppose to give you a bunch of links to themes or ready implementations of documentation portals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Hall of Fame</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/hardware/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/hardware/projects/</guid>
      <description>This page collects various Open Hardware projects. These projects are not officially endorsed, but are listed here as a convenience to generate a list of examples for reference. For more detailed overviews, see the Case Studies page.
 Check out the list of certified hardware from the Open Source Hardware Association for more inspiration.
 Businesses &amp;amp; companies   Adafruit Industries
  Aleph Objects: Makers of LulzBot family of 3D printers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
