<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Open Source Mentorship on UNICEF O.S. Inventory</title>
    <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/meta/mentorship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Open Source Mentorship on UNICEF O.S. Inventory</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Creative Commons BY-SA 4.0. Site theme maintained by UNICEF. Original theme, Dot, created by ThemeFisher.</copyright><atom:link href="https://unicef.github.io/inventory/meta/mentorship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Mentorship programme overview</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/meta/mentorship/overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/meta/mentorship/overview/</guid>
      <description>This page documents and explains the general structure, approach, and methods of the Open Source Mentorship programme hosted on this website. The Open Source Mentorship programme is offered by the UNICEF Innovation Fund. See the table of contents for navigating.
  Programme team
  Eligibility
 Innovation Fund grantees
  UNICEF colleagues
  Other groups
     References
   1. Programme team The Open Source Mentorship programme is administered by the Innovation Fund Open Source Technical Advisor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modules</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/meta/mentorship/modules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/meta/mentorship/modules/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents 1. Offered modules 1.1. Legal &amp;amp; Licensing: Foundations of Open Source intellectual property 1.2. Launching your Open Source project 1.3. Open Source documentation 1.4. Continuous Integration for continuous contribution 1.5. Archetypes: Shape and size of Open Source over time   2. Module programming 2.1. 12-month Innovation Fund contracts     The UNICEF Open Source Mentorship programme offers multiple learning modules and mentorship topics. This page provides an overview of the different modules currently offered through the Open Source Mentorship programme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Needs assessment interview template</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/meta/mentorship/needs-assessment-template/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/meta/mentorship/needs-assessment-template/</guid>
      <description>This document is an interview template for needs assessments with UNICEF Innovation Fund cohorts in Open Source induction calls. The needs assessment is a tool to collect background and context for each team’s experience and familiarity with open source. It also builds understanding for participation in existing open source communities. This template provides structure and guidance on what to ask to any team at the beginning of an Open Source Mentorship program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On-boarding guide for UNICEF Innovation Fund teams</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/meta/mentorship/onboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/meta/mentorship/onboarding/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents 1. Summary of UNICEF Open Source Mentorship 1.1. Monthly 60m check-ins 1.2. Ad-hoc 30m meetings   2. Meet the Inventory 3. Topics covered in Open Source Mentorship   This document is for teams newly joining the UNICEF Innovation Fund. It provides a high-level overview to the UNICEF Open Source Mentorship programme, a unique perk and strategic asset of being a UNICEF investee.
 1. Summary of UNICEF Open Source Mentorship Your assigned Open Source Mentor from the Innovation Fund can be found on the programme team list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Templates for programme mentors</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/meta/mentorship/templates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/meta/mentorship/templates/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents 1. Induction agenda template 2. Initial research template 3. Email summary template   This page is a copy-paste template of various templates I use for Open Source Mentorship meetings. I use these for my private notes about each team’s progress.
 1. Induction agenda template   Agenda:
  Introductions
  Offer to record call
  Review O.S. Terms of Reference
  Review frequently-used resources (i.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workplan: Bridge Fund cohort</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/meta/mentorship/workplan-bridge-funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory/meta/mentorship/workplan-bridge-funding/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents 1. Mission 2. Vision 3. Community 4. Timeline 4.1. Q1 4.2. Q2 4.3. Q3 4.4. Q4   5. References   This page documents the workplan requirements for the Bridge Fund cohort of the UNICEF Innovation Fund. These graduation expectations are in place for UNICEF grantees receiving follow-on funding from UNICEF. See the table of contents for navigating.
 1. Mission Bridging humanitarian Open Source works and communities to the wider Open Source ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
